http://lkdaerospace.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
LKDAerospace.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting LKDAerospace.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
What Personal Information About Customers Does LKDAerospace.com Gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at LKDAerospace.com. Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use “cookies,” and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses LKDAerospace.com. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at LKDAerospace.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.
E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from LKDAerospace.com if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Account Preferences.
Information from Other Sources For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.
What About Cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as automatic login, customized product displays and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits. The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of LKDAerospace.com’s coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.
Does LKDAerospace.com Share the Information It Receives?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with the subsidiaries LKD Aerospace Inc. controls and as described below.
Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: We work closely with our affiliated businesses, an example of which is our distribution partners, such as Ametek Aerospace, our Rotables supplier. In some cases, these businesses operate stores at LKDAerospace.com or sell offerings to you at LKDAerospace.com. In other cases, we operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with these businesses. You can tell when another business is involved in your transactions, and we share customer information related to those transactions with that business.
Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Promotional Offers: Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of LKDAerospace.com customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please adjust your Account Preferences.
Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or acquire businesses or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that LKDAerospace.com, Inc., or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
Protection of LKDAerospace.com and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of LKDAerospace.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. LKD does not store credit card information. We believe this process provides enhanced security that is worth the inconvenience of re-inputting your credit card information.
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
What Information Can I Access?
LKDAerospace.com gives you access to the following information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. This list will change as our Web site evolves.
What Choices Do I Have?
As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such LKDAerospace.com features as access to pricing information and establishing pricing discounts, as well as access to Premier Partners and other information services.
You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the “What Information Can I Access?” section above. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust Your Account Preferences. (If you do not want to receive Terms and Conditions and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of LKDAerospace.com, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.)
The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you will not be able to use such important features as access to pricing or automatic login capabilities if you do not use cookies.
The Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own Web site, Site Seeing on the Internet.
Children
LKDAerospace.com does not sell products for purchase by children. All of our products and services are used in the support of aircraft, aerospace or aviation services. If you are under 18, you may use LKDAerospace.com only with involvement of a parent or guardian.
Terms and Conditions, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit LKDAerospace.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Washington. If you have any concern about privacy at LKDAerospace.com, please send us a thorough description to Webmaster@Lkdaero.com, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms and Conditions will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
Recent Posts
LKD Aerospace Achieves Aerospace Industry’s AS9100D Certification
Recent CommentsArchives
July 2018
Categories
Uncategorized
Meta
Log in
Entries feed
Comments feed
About Us
LKD Aerospace is a Global Distributor, Manufacturer & MRO of Aerospace Components
We specialize in distribution of aircraft spares, FAA PMA parts, MRO services and OEM manufacturing of aerospace components for a variety of applications.
LKD Aerospace - Headquarters:
